let mediumdivisionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 100 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "18",
        AnswerB: "20",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "20",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 120 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 140 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 180 ÷ 10",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 150 ÷ 25",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 135 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 110 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 121 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "12",
        AnswerD: "13",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 12",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "16",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 ÷ 13",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 76 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 108 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 128 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 129 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "11",
        AnswerC: "12",
        AnswerD: "13",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 52 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 171 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "17",
        AnswerB: "19",
        AnswerC: "21",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 153 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 174 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "29",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "15",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 95 ÷ 5",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 162 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "14",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 111 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 228 ÷ 12",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 189 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 114 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 156 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 154 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "22",
    },
]